Blade.
So here you are.
Sophie.
I've always wanted to go
all out in a fight against you.
Can I win if I don't hold back?
Why don't we find out?
Okay, then.
Artificial Great Hero Power.
Stop the flow of time.
Ten seconds.
How?
You can attack me a hundred times, but if each
does zero damage, that still makes zero.
Adamantine Body.
A technique that momentarily
increases the toughness of your body.
Since you stopped time,
it was active all along.
I see.
I'm an ordinary citizen now,
so I thought I'd be done with all of this.
I look in your eyes, and I'm met with
A brand-new me and dream
Bravery? Naturally?
Polar opposites within the heart
But, you know, wanting to have both
That's the saga of human nature
Oh no, don't mind me
Go ahead, and so on, you know the rest
A little more? Wait, even harder?!
Going overboard much?
Those selfish emotions deep down
Bringing them to light is
what friendship's about
Spending adolescence duking it out with pals
I don't wanna lose
We're off to the cutting edge moment
Fight with best friends, and leave no regrets
You should laugh, since
you look best with a smile
On the ropes?! No matter
what we face, et cetera
Just sit back and enjoy it
Whatever may come, I'll
be here to protect you
Episode 7
The Springtime of Life
at Rosewood Academy
Hey, old man!
I don't know what kind of
magic or trickery this is,
but can't we call it quits already?!
I believe I explained it all at the start.
This is no trickery.
This technology known as virtual reality
was made using a lost branch
of magic known as science.
Also, and I mentioned this as well,
there's no need to use a blunted sword
or to stop yourself at the
last second as you do in reality.
That is to say, it's practical
training like you've never seen it!
Dragons are the strongest!
A dragon whelp like you dares to face me?
Train as hard as you can in this practicum,
until there is only one left standing.
It's a fight to the death!
What a sick joke.
That's fine and all, but can
you make it easier to distinguish?
I can't tell the difference!
Distinguish between what?
It's way too realistic!
The way it is now, even after we go back,
there's bound to be someone who thinks
they're still in virtua-whatsit,
and slaughters their friends!
That would not do.
Well, how about this, then?
Okay, keep on fighting hard from here on out!
The last one standing gets the right to use
virtual reality however they want as a reward!
Guess I have no choice
but to end this quickly.
My lord dearest!
The honor of facing you in combat is mine—
Ow!
Even as you tear me to pieces...
how beautiful you are!
Where are you, Blade?
Hi-yah!
Yessica!
Give it up already.
Ever since our days in the lower classes,
you've never beaten us in a fight.
That may be so, but you
never know until you try!
Yep. The winner is whoever's stronger now!
So, Clay...
Why do you refuse to lose to us?
Huh?! Well, that's...
Shoot—
Ono!
Kassim!
Uchida!
Huh? W-We won?
We really won?
Yay!
I've been looking for you, Blade.
I never knew that killing
people was this much fun!
I've been so stupid,
holding back all this time!
I guess I did promise
that if you ever went berserk, I would...
cut you down!
Keheheh!
Endless Flash!
I'm Blade!
We know.
It looks like you were the
last one standing after all.
Well done, Parent!
I couldn't even tell what
he did there at the end.
Yeah.
It was so sudden,
I didn't even feel any pain.
I can't believe it!
To think I behaved like that...
Oh yeah, you were laughing like, "Keheheh!"
Shut up!
Be quiet,
you superorganism!
No, I'm as ordinary as can be!
Wallowing in misery is yet
another part of youth!
Youth is a splendid thing, indeed!
This is all thanks to my brilliant idea!
Your Majesty.
Do you know how much trouble
we've faced thanks to your brilliant idea?
Oh? Going to have fun with it already?
It's your right as the victor!
Enjoy it to the fullest!
Oh? Is that data of ferocious demons?
Yep.
Scattered all throughout the level?
Booby-trapped floors?
Yep.
Hold on.
Don't you think these settings are
a little too extreme, even for you?
It's fine.
Huh?
Can you make him keep on
respawning, even if he dies?
Yes, I can.
How long should I continue his punishment?
Until nightfall, then.
Certainly.
I'm starving! Let's go get lunch!
Mmm! Delicious!
Tonkatsu curry is so good!
What the heck? It never stops!
Hey, you two.
When are you gonna get over it?
That's right.
Did something happen?
Those four had a tag match,
and the girls won.
What led to the girls winning?
Claire's gotten way better.
Th-That's not true!
As well as Yessica's do-or-die attack.
A woman's gotta be daring!
What led to the boys losing, then?
Probably their complacency
about their skills.
They got conceited and
neglected their training.
Not mincing your words, huh?
It's for their own good.
My back! My back! My back!
When did the king get around to
building something like this?
Oh! I've been waiting for you, Great—
I mean, Blade!
So, what in the world
is this "thermae" thing?
It says—
Allow me to explain!
Who are you?
I'm Eliza!
Well, in any case,
you'll know when you go inside!
Welcome to Thermae Rosewood!
So these are thermae!
A nice, big bath isn't bad, either!
This is fun!
Sophie, let's swim!
Is that a command?
Three hero-level warriors were
summoned here to dig these baths.
I can't believe that old fogey.
Ya-ha!
Ya-ha.
You're not Mao today?
If I switched with Mao,
she would take off the swimsuit.
What's wrong with that?
What?!
Not all the guys here are
five-year-olds, you know.
Oh, yeah.
Where's Earnest?
Ah, I bet she didn't come.
She seemed against it.
I-I'm right here!
Mixed bathing?
H-How indecent!
How shameless!
Looks like you're all enjoying the thermae!
Your Majesty?!
Please cover yourself!
What are you saying?
Thermae are meant to be entered in the nude!
We need swimsuits, since it's mixed bathing!
Gil.
I guess I have to accept that.
I can accept swimsuits...
However!
Don't wear a towel in the bath!
What?!
It's a part of our kingdom's constitution!
Thou shalt not wear towels in the bath!
Since when?!
Are you an idiot?!
Since three seconds ago!
Gil. There's nothing of the
sort in our constitution...
I want to see naked girls!
I'd do anything to see them naked!
But if that's not possible...
I at least want to see them in swimsuits!
Don't you all agree?
We do!
That's the spirit!
Hey!
You guys!
C'mon, Anna, can't you just take it off?
Besides, hasn't the value of seeing
you naked plummeted already?
Plummeted?!
I mean, during the simurgh incident,
you were running around town buck naked!
That was because I was fighting!
I have no clue why you're still embarrassed.
I wouldn't want to take off my swimsuit,
but what's wrong with taking off the towel?
Everyone else already has.
My lord!
Yeah, yeah!
Claire's totally right!
Why does the Empress get special treatment?!
Take it off! Take it off!
Wait...
I'm not taking it off!
Strip her! Strip her!
Take it off!
Just take it all off!
Lay bare your youthful, nude form!
If you won't take it off,
I'll amend the constitution!
From now on, wearing any clothes
in this kingdom will be—
Hello! Splash!
Everyone, I'm terribly sorry about this.
Sheesh! I just have to take it off, right?
I can take this towel off just fine!
Don't stare at me too much.
Sure, I won't look.
U-Um...
Do you have a minute?
What happened earlier today...
Y-You shouldn't worry about it so much.
That was just a fluke.
I'm sure of it, I think...
No. We were just thinking about it again now.
It was all because of our lack of skills...
No way!
You two really are way stronger than us!
Hey, Blade...
What?
You know how people talk about
"rubbing salt in the wound"?
Yeah.
I think I now truly understand what it means.
Me, too.
Um, so...
I'm sorry for winning!
You made them cry.
She sure did.
Yes, she did.
Clay and Kassim are hopeless!
Aw, man.
Hey, cheer up already!
All you did was lose once!
You wouldn't understand.
You've never lost to a girl!
More like, you don't lose to anyone.
Being a superorganism and all.
I don't let it get to me when I lose.
Well, I can't stand it!
I wouldn't mind if it was anyone else.
But I don't want to lose against Yessica!
Yessica? Why her?
Isn't it obvious?!
I... l-like Yessica!
I like Yessica, too.
What?!
I thought you liked Earnest, or Sophie!
I like them, too!
As well as Cu and Maria.
I like you and everyone else, too.
Eh?!
Oh, I see. That kind of like.
That's not what we're talking about here.
How's it different?
See here!
I'm sure you've figured
it out, but I like Claire!
Claire... she's so great.
She comes off as just your typical girl...
but she can be ruthless sometimes,
which is good in its own way!
I see. I don't get it.
Yessica, too!
She seems so free and uninhibited,
and I bet she's got tons of experience.
I see. I really don't get it.
But despite all that,
she's really kind and caring!
Claire as well!
I do get that part.
So that's what was troubling you?
The answer is simple!
You two just need to get stronger!
Huh?
Listen up!
Females are attracted to strong males!
Get stronger, and they'll be all over you!
Head over heels for you!
Cu, be a little more serious here—
Sh-She's right!
Yeah!
But how are we supposed to get stronger?
That's simple as well!
You just need special training from Parent!
Ah! That's right!
Mmm, so tasty!
This cake is good, right?
And chock-full of calories!
Oh, no!
No, no, no!
Um, Anna...
We're having a girls'
night tonight because...
Look, it's so delicious!
Is it about Clay and Kassim?
I can't imagine life without sweets anymore!
It's really been a pain.
They've been running away from us ever since.
I don't think it's a big deal
to lose to someone once.
Seriously, getting bummed
out from just that...
Why are boys so fragile?
Oh, what if we lost to them on purpose?
You really shouldn't do that.
They won't be able to recover from that.
Huh? That's no good?
What should we do, then?
The answer is simple!
Males are attracted to strong females!
Get stronger, and they'll be all over you!
Head over heels for you!
Wait, we're not trying
to make them fall for us.
That's right. We don't see them that way.
Huh? You don't?
Hey, Yessica...
Why don't we skip practice,
and let those two get stronger than us?
No! Absolutely not!
Hey, are you two really okay
with things as they are?
Well, no, but...
Mm-hmm...
How about this, then?
1,141! 1,142! 1,143!
These are the lightest we have!
Work those core muscles!
That's amazing.
It's finally time.
Well, no matter the outcome,
I can at least confirm that
you haven't neglected your training!
If we win this battle...
Yeah!
We'll confess to them!
Confess!
No hard feelings, no matter who wins.
Are you ready?
Okay!
Begin!
Claire! Here we go!
Yeah!
Coming at us?
No, you don't!
Take this!
Blade, did you teach them how
to use their fighting spirit?
I just made them realize they've been
subconsciously using fighting spirit all along.
Also...
Kassim is using wind spiritual energy.
Hmm...
My chance!
Fire spiritual energy?!
Did you teach her that?
Just the fire part.
Guh!
Fighting spirit?!
There!
So it ends here...
Next, it's...
Huh?
My turn!
I'm sorry.
Well, dang.
You got us good.
Thanks for not going easy on us.
Yeah.
We're going to get even stronger.
You go do that.
Fighting's not even our specialty, you know.
Hey...
Did Sophie and Maria teach you how to
use ice and lightning spiritual energy?
You got it.
The other girls helped us out as well.
Seriously?
That's not fair, all of you ganging up on us.
Don't give me that!
How can you call it unfair,
being taught by the superorganism?!
Why's she angry?
And there's something
I need to say to you two!
Huh?
Is it wrong to fall in love with someone
unless you're stronger than them?
Or confess to them?!
You've gotta be kidding!
That's just asking for way too much!
The sunny disposition that
brings a smile to your face
As well as the heroic sense of justice
They may be a part of me,
but that's not all there is
That image of me
Has taken on a life of its own
Hey, wait up
Won't you be friends with me?
Let's shake hands, another self of mine
The wounds we cannot bear alone
The dangers that we keep hidden
We're all hiding them within
Standing ready to strike
The shadow lurking beneath the light
The muffled sounds coming from my lips
They make me feel that I am alive
It's a sign
Next Time
Less Than Human